大家好！在瞬息萬變的世界中，情緒敏捷是一項至關重要的核心素養。
當我們帶著情緒敏捷生活時，我們能涵養出深層智慧，更有效地去愛、領導與育兒。以下是情緒敏捷的四大核心維度（4Cs）：
第一是 Compassion（自我慈悲）：生而為人並不容易，在受挫時請給予自己寬厚、關愛與尊嚴；
第二是 Courage（勇氣）：迎向困難需要勇氣，踐行價值觀與面對痛苦情緒都需要勇氣。請記住，勇氣不一定大聲喧嘩，有時勇氣只是一聲輕柔的低語與自我關愛；
第三是 Curiosity（好奇心）：當我們對世界與自我敞開好奇時，我們拓展了生命的格局。對外探索世界，對內覺察情緒背後的路標；
第四是 Centeredness（內在定錨）：當外在環境動盪劇變時，我們需要牢牢立足於內在。這並不意味著你隨時都有現成答案，而是你永遠知道如何回歸真實的自我。
isn't always loud. Sometimes courage is a whisper. It's the reassurance and it's the love
that you give to yourself. Number three is curiosity. When we are curious in the world,
when we are open to growth and learning, we expand our capacity. And one way of being curious
is external. Another way of being curious is internal. See when you experience difficult emotions
if you can recognize what those emotions are signposting. We might, for example,
when we feel lonely, see only the lonely. And yet the lonely is often signaling that we need more
connection and intimacy in our lives. It's a beautiful invitation to walk more towards that thing.
And last is centeredness. When the world is changing around us, we need to be grounded in ourselves.
It doesn't mean that you always have the answer or always know the path, but you always know that you
will come back to you.